

am writing to express my interest in the **REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER** position that you have posted. I believe that my experience and skills make me a strong candidate for this position.

I have been developing software for over 5 years, with a focus on mobile development for the last 4 years. My experience includes developing native applications for iOS and Android as well as cross-platform applications using React Native and flutter. I have also developed web apps using React js and other React js libraries.

My core strengths include being able to quickly learn new technologies, being able to work independently or as part of a team, and being able to communicate effectively with both technical and non-technical people. I am also skilled at troubleshooting bugs and finding solutions to difficult problems.

I would like to thank you for your consideration and look forward to hearing from you soon.

# **NOTE:**

My field of study is not related to computer science but I have the experience as it is my passion to learn and develop software application. you will find below my CV (Resume) link to the various work I have done on github



# Hanafi Taofiq

# **REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER**

Dynamic and innovative professional with 4+ years of invaluable hands-on experience in handling several simulteneous creative design projects, concept creation, graphics design, web design and mobile app development with react native. Equipped with the ability to escalate brand awareness by utilizing skills gained in the creative industry, being able to identify opportunities, overcome objections, build long-term mutually beneficial relationships with vendors, workforce and clients. establishing a successful and lucrative company

2016 - 2022

2013 - 2015

2008 - 2013

2000 - 2006

2023

Mar., 2021

Mar., 2021

Nov., 2019

MOBILE	NO.		

**PERMANENT ADDRESS** SEX:

D.O.B

**EMAIL** 

08159832838,09032339903

Male

Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria

1995

ayodejiokoh@gmail.com

B.Ed ISLAMIC STUDIES	
Ahmadu Bello University Zaria, Kaduna Sta	te

**EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND** 

**DIPLOMA IN ENGLISH & ISLAMIC STUDIES** 

College of Arabic and Islamic Legal Studies Ilorin, Kwara State

SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE Asa Local Gov't Sec. School Budo Tuntun

PRIMARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

Igra Nur/pri School Ilorin, Kwara State

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORP(NYSC)

Airforce Comprehensive School Uyo

ANDROID APPLICATION DEVELOPER

**GREAT LEARNING** online program

JAVA PROGRAMMING

**GREAT LEARNING** online program

**HTML & CSS** 

**TEMPLATE MONSTER** online program

SU	ΗI	VV /	4K	ES	/וט	E

A2 CODE	100%
ANDROID STUDIO	100%

**CORELDRAW** 100%

**PHOTOSHOP** 95%

100%

#### **HOOBIES**

**MS WORD** 

SPORT, CODING,

**DEBUGGING,, DESIGNING,** 

**RESEARCHING** 

# **LANGUAGES**

YORUBA	100%
ENGLISH	80%
ARABIC	50%

### **SKILLS**

HTML 5	100%
CSS 3	100%
JAVASCRIPT	100%
RESTFUL API	100%

REACT JS	100%
MATERIAL UI	100%
NODE JS	100%
MONGODB	100%

100%
100%
100%

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

Design and implement user interface components for JavaScript-based web and mobile applications.

Work as a part of a small team that includes other react native developers, designers, QA experts, and managers

Build app and UI components from prototypes and wireframes

Work with native modules as and when required

Use Native APIs for tight integrations with both platforms – Android and iOS

Write automated tests to ensure error-free code and performance

Improve front-end performance by eliminating performance bottlenecks

Create front-end modules with maximum code reusability and efficiency

Implement clean, smooth animations to provide an excellent user interface

Work with third-party dependencies and APIs

Work with Redux architecture to improve performance of the websites/mobile apps

Coordinate with the cross-functional teams to build apps in stipulated time/budget.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER (REMOTE) 2020 - 2023 ASYNC TECHNOLOGY,

No 20 Fate Road, Ilorin, Kwara State. Nigeria

# GRAPHICS DESIGNER 2019 - 2020

Ajenifuja printing press, Ilorin Kwara State

# GRAPHICS & MOTION DESIGNER 2016 - 2019

No 39 Benin Street, Sabon Gari Zaria, Kaduna State

# REFERENCES

- PROF. FATIMAH IBRAHIM Senior Lecturer, ABU Zaria 08023327728
- MR. HANAFI MUHAMMED OKOH Banker, Ilorin Kwara State 08038882265
- DR. HANAFI ABDULRAZAQ OKOH
  H.O.D, Health Technology Offa
  08023327728
- DR. HANAFI FADHILAT OKOH
  Retired L.G.A Civil Servant
  08063109461